http://www.raylenvineyards.com/privacy-policy/

Event DetailsJoin us for our exclusive members only Holiday Party!
Enjoy live music by Darrell Hoots and heavy hors d'oeuvres while celebrating the holiday season with fellow RayLen Club Members.
Tickets are
Event Details
Join us for our exclusive members only Holiday Party!
Enjoy live music by Darrell Hoots and heavy hors d’oeuvres while celebrating the holiday season with fellow RayLen Club Members.
Tickets are $30.00 per couple and will be applied to a case purchase the day of the party.  Tickets may be purchased by calling The Tasting Room at 336-998-3100.
*For current Case Club, Cork Club, and Premier Cru Club Members only.
Don’t forget to check out our upcoming calendar.
Have questions? Check out our FAQs page
Time(Friday) 6:00 pm - 9:00 pm
CalendarGoogleCal
Pack the Sack Drive-Thru Benefit
12dec11:00 am5:00 pmPack the Sack Drive-Thru Benefit11:00 am - 5:00 pm
Event DetailsHelp us Pack the Sack as we partner with Bermuda Run Cares, Transou Rooter & Plumbing, the Plumb Positive Show, and Bermuda Run Living to support
Event Details
Help us Pack the Sack as we partner with Bermuda Run Cares, Transou Rooter & Plumbing, the Plumb Positive Show, and Bermuda Run Living to support the Storehouse for Jesus! Drop off your gently used children’s coasts, canned foods, and hygiene products. We will also have live music by Red Umber and food for purchase from Salsarita’s food truck from noon-5pm. So join us December 12th and DONATE, EAT, DRINK, AND BE MERRY!!
For more information on this event, please call (336) 817-6047 or email bermudaruncares@gmail.com.
Pack the Sack is open to the public. Please respect 6 foot social distancing between groups of 10 or less and remember masks are required.
Feel free to bring a lawn chair! NO outside alcohol, food, coolers, balls, scooters, or bicycles are permitted. Rain or Shine.
Don’t forget to check out our upcoming calendar.
Have questions? Check out our FAQs page
Time(Saturday) 11:00 am - 5:00 pm
CalendarGoogleCal
Holiday Open House
19dec12:00 pm4:00 pmHoliday Open House12:00 pm - 4:00 pm
Event DetailsJoin us with your family this Christmas season for our Holiday Open House.
Enjoy holiday themed festivities from live Christmas music from Tyler and Emma and even a visit
Event Details
Join us with your family this Christmas season for our Holiday Open House.
Enjoy holiday themed festivities from live Christmas music from Tyler and Emma and even a visit with Santa and Mrs. Claus!
Tyler and Emma will be performing music from noon-3pm, followed by a reading of ‘Twas the Night Before Christmas by Santa. Warm up with a cup of hot chocolate with all the fixings from our hot chocolate station and enjoy some sweet treats from Cherry on Top. The Wicked Awesome food truck will also be onsite serving up some deliciously awesome food.
Interested in a visit with Santa? Come take your picture with Santa and share your Christmas wish with a handwritten letter. *All visits with Santa and Mrs. Claus will be socially distanced*
In the spirit of Christmas, we will also be collecting toys for Toys for Tots. Help put a smile on a child’s face this holiday season!
Holiday Open House is open to the public. Please respect 6 foot social distancing between groups of 10 or less and remember masks are required.
Feel free to bring a lawn chair! NO outside alcohol, food, coolers, balls, scooters, or bicycles are permitted. Rain or Shine.
Don’t forget to check out our upcoming calendar.
Have questions? Check out our FAQs page
Time(Saturday) 12:00 pm - 4:00 pm
CalendarGoogleCal
See All Events
Wines & More
Wines
Tastings & Tours
Case Club
Shop
FAQ
Events
I have a question about and upcoming event.
Are dogs allowed?
Can I bring outside food and drink?
Tours & Tastings
Can I visit the vineyard to pick my own grapes?
How much is a tasting?
Will I be able to schedule a tour today?
Other
What hours are you open?
Can guests bring beer and outside alcohol?
How do I make a return or cancel a purchased event ticket?
Shop
All Wines
Whites
Reds
Limited
Gift Cards & Tastings
Blog
Contact Us
Member Holiday Party
11dec6:00 pm9:00 pmEvent CancelledMember Holiday Party6:00 pm - 9:00 pm
Event DetailsJoin us for our exclusive members only Holiday Party!
Enjoy live music by Darrell Hoots and heavy hors d'oeuvres while celebrating the holiday season with fellow RayLen Club Members.
Tickets are
Event Details
Join us for our exclusive members only Holiday Party!
Enjoy live music by Darrell Hoots and heavy hors d’oeuvres while celebrating the holiday season with fellow RayLen Club Members.
Tickets are $30.00 per couple and will be applied to a case purchase the day of the party.  Tickets may be purchased by calling The Tasting Room at 336-998-3100.
*For current Case Club, Cork Club, and Premier Cru Club Members only.
Don’t forget to check out our upcoming calendar.
Have questions? Check out our FAQs page
Time(Friday) 6:00 pm - 9:00 pm
CalendarGoogleCal
Pack the Sack Drive-Thru Benefit
12dec11:00 am5:00 pmPack the Sack Drive-Thru Benefit11:00 am - 5:00 pm
Event DetailsHelp us Pack the Sack as we partner with Bermuda Run Cares, Transou Rooter & Plumbing, the Plumb Positive Show, and Bermuda Run Living to support
Event Details
Help us Pack the Sack as we partner with Bermuda Run Cares, Transou Rooter & Plumbing, the Plumb Positive Show, and Bermuda Run Living to support the Storehouse for Jesus! Drop off your gently used children’s coasts, canned foods, and hygiene products. We will also have live music by Red Umber and food for purchase from Salsarita’s food truck from noon-5pm. So join us December 12th and DONATE, EAT, DRINK, AND BE MERRY!!
For more information on this event, please call (336) 817-6047 or email bermudaruncares@gmail.com.
Pack the Sack is open to the public. Please respect 6 foot social distancing between groups of 10 or less and remember masks are required.
Feel free to bring a lawn chair! NO outside alcohol, food, coolers, balls, scooters, or bicycles are permitted. Rain or Shine.
Don’t forget to check out our upcoming calendar.
Have questions? Check out our FAQs page
Time(Saturday) 11:00 am - 5:00 pm
CalendarGoogleCal
Holiday Open House
19dec12:00 pm4:00 pmHoliday Open House12:00 pm - 4:00 pm
Event DetailsJoin us with your family this Christmas season for our Holiday Open House.
Enjoy holiday themed festivities from live Christmas music from Tyler and Emma and even a visit
Event Details
Join us with your family this Christmas season for our Holiday Open House.
Enjoy holiday themed festivities from live Christmas music from Tyler and Emma and even a visit with Santa and Mrs. Claus!
Tyler and Emma will be performing music from noon-3pm, followed by a reading of ‘Twas the Night Before Christmas by Santa. Warm up with a cup of hot chocolate with all the fixings from our hot chocolate station and enjoy some sweet treats from Cherry on Top. The Wicked Awesome food truck will also be onsite serving up some deliciously awesome food.
Interested in a visit with Santa? Come take your picture with Santa and share your Christmas wish with a handwritten letter. *All visits with Santa and Mrs. Claus will be socially distanced*
In the spirit of Christmas, we will also be collecting toys for Toys for Tots. Help put a smile on a child’s face this holiday season!
Holiday Open House is open to the public. Please respect 6 foot social distancing between groups of 10 or less and remember masks are required.
Feel free to bring a lawn chair! NO outside alcohol, food, coolers, balls, scooters, or bicycles are permitted. Rain or Shine.
Don’t forget to check out our upcoming calendar.
Have questions? Check out our FAQs page
Time(Saturday) 12:00 pm - 4:00 pm
CalendarGoogleCal
See All Events
Wines & More
Wines
Tastings & Tours
Case Club
Shop
FAQ
Events
I have a question about and upcoming event.
Are dogs allowed?
Can I bring outside food and drink?
Tours & Tastings
Can I visit the vineyard to pick my own grapes?
How much is a tasting?
Will I be able to schedule a tour today?
Other
What hours are you open?
Can guests bring beer and outside alcohol?
How do I make a return or cancel a purchased event ticket?
Shop
All Wines
Whites
Reds
Limited
Gift Cards & Tastings
Blog
Contact Us
(336) 998-3100
Privacy Policy
PRIVACY POLICY AND TERMS OF USE
At RayLen Vineyards Inc, we recognize and respect our customers’ privacy and diligently protect the trust you have placed in us. We have developed a Privacy Policy to assure you that the information collected about you is only what is needed for conducting business and offering products and services that might be of interest to you. As a user of this site, you are agreeing to these policies.  The privacy of those who visit our website is of primary concern to RayLen Vineyards, Inc. Except as noted, none of this information is shared with outside parties. What information is gathered, how it is obtained, and what it is used for is explained below. If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at (336) 998-3100 or email erin@raylenvineyards.com.
VISIT INFORMATION
Like many companies, RayLen Vineyards automatically tracks the usage of our website. We profile website usage by tracking the pages viewed, the frequency of visits, the browser used ISP and the region our visitors come from. This information is used to analyze trends, track use, and optimize site administration and is not tied to any identifiable person or account. For visits only your activity is anonymous.
REGISTRATION INFORMATION
By purchasing wine from our website, you are consenting to the Privacy Policy and Terms of Use. In order to purchase wine from our website, you must first complete the registration form. During registration, you are required to give certain contact information (such as name, email address) and create a password. This information is used to contact you about the services on our site for which you have expressed interest (your purchase information will never include your credit card information). You may opt out of receiving communications from us either during registration, or at any other time by emailing us at erin@raylenvineyards.com, or by calling us at (336) 998-3100. We require you to verify your age in order to purchase.
SECURED PURCHASE INFORMATION
When a credit card order is placed on our website, your name, billing address, shipping address, telephone number, credit card number and expiration date are gathered. This is used to verify payment authorization, process your order, personalize your shopping experience, inform you of deliveries, deliver the merchandise to the proper destination and generate statistics. RayLen Vineyards takes numerous precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, the information is protected both online and offline.
For all purchase information, RayLen Vineyards uses Secure Socket Layer (SSL) underneath HTTP, providing an encrypted channel and server authentication, so that all such information is transmitted through a secured server connection. Before your order is processed online, your browser will make a confirmed identification that the transmission of all data is being made between your computer and with RayLen Vineyards. While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also take several steps to protect your information offline. All of your information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a Customer Service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. If you have any questions about the security of our website, you can email us at erin@raylenvineyards.com or call us at (336) 998-3100.
COMMUNICATIONS
RayLen Vineyards is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. RayLen Vineyards collects information from you at several different points on our website. As a purchaser, you should expect to receive an email confirming your order, an email confirming your shipment, an electronic receipt and a paper receipt (which accompanies your order).
As a customer of RayLen Vineyards, you have the option to receive RayLen Vineyards newsletters via email. We also communicate with you on a regular basis to provide requested services. We reply to your inquiries on issues relating to your account via email or phone. For instance, when you use the “Contact Us” link, we use this information solely to respond to your questions and comments and to improve our customer service.
On rare occasions, it is necessary to send out a strictly service-related announcement. For instance, if we discovered an error during your visit to our site that prevented you from completing a purchase, we might send you an email to let you know our site is back in service. Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications and they are not promotional in nature. However, you may deactivate your account.
We employ other companies to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and processing credit card payments. They have access only to the personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.
At registration, you may opt in to receiving newsletter communications from RayLen Vineyards. After registration, you may also opt out of receiving communications from RayLen Vineyards by clicking the ”Unsubscribe“ link provided in our emails to you, emailing us erin@raylenvineards.com or by calling us at (336) 998-3100. Please allow up to 3 weeks to process your request.
RayLen Vineyards’ website may have links to other websites on the Internet that are not owned or controlled by RayLen Vineyards. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or the content of these websites, nor does this mean that RayLen Vineyards endorses them in any way.
CORRECTING, UPDATING AND DELETING INFORMATION
RayLen Vineyards cannot guarantee that all private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right and may be forced to disclose any and all information to government bodies or government officials or third parties under certain circumstances or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. Accordingly, you authorize RayLen Vineyards to disclose any and all information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate, in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements or other activity that is illegal or may expose us to legal liability.
Further, you authorize RayLen Vineyards to disclose your password, name, street address, city, state, zip code, country, phone number, email address and company as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, gray market, intellectual property infringement, piracy or other unlawful activity. Specifically, this includes exchanging such information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. RayLen Vineyards cooperates with law enforcement inquiries and other third parties to enforce laws, intellectual property and other rights.
DISCLOSURE TO AUTHORITIES
If your personally identifiable information (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address) changes, or if you no longer desire to belong on our mailing list, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate your personally identifiable information. This can usually be done online or by emailing erin@raylenvineyards.com or calling (336)998-3100.
COOKIES
Cookies are small pieces of information sent from a Web server to your computer. These allow us to personalize, customize and quickly process and complete your shopping experience without having to continually request the same basic information from you. For example, we use cookies to track the items in your Shopping Cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on your site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved service.
Cookies are not used to store any personal information such as name, address or payment information.
If you do not accept or if you remove our cookies, you will not be able to make a purchase on our site. However, you may still call to place your order at (336) 998-3100.
LIMITATION OF LIABILITY
TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, RAYLEN VINEYARDS SHALL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES OR ANY LOSS, WHETHER INCURRED DIRECTLY OR INDIRECTLY, OR ANY LOSS OF DATA, USE, OR GOODWILL, OR OTHER INTANGIBLE LOSSES, RESULTING FROM YOUR ACCESS TO OR USE OF OR INABILITY TO ACCESS OR USE THE SITE OR ANY CONDUCT OR CONTENT OF ANY THIRD PARTY ON THE SITE.
We’re always looking for ways to improve our site’s features and services and to improve the way we communicate our information practices. As a result, these policies are updated from time to time. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.
We now ship to additional states!
AK, AZ, GA, HI, IA, ID, IL, IN, KS, MA, MD, ME, MO, ND, NE, NM, NV, OH, OK, OR, PA, TN, VT, WA, WI, WV, WY
Order Now
X
